### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/marieantonette-mendoza-45a1b5271 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Dancing Social Games Talk shows

# Marie Antonette Mendoza

A highly trainable individual who's always passionate and enthusiastic to learn new things for continuous career growth and self development. Hard work, commitment and dedication complement a strong desire to do the job.

Agusan del Norte, Caraga, Philippines

## Summary

A well experienced Customer Service Professional for 4 years and 2 months through several BPO Call Center Industries. A passionate and well experienced ESL Teacher for 1 year and 8 months. A passionate freelance singer in any private events and occasions, who has many experiences performing in front of large audiences such as LGU related events, programs and concerts together with the city band. I'm also currently doing live streaming in social media apps, singing and entertaining online audiences. As a versatile person, I'm always eager to learn and experience new things such as doing Voice Talent jobs like Voice acting and voice overs.

## Experience

### Kumu

Livestreamer/Host March 2021 - Present (3 years 10 months)

### LGU CABADBARAN CITY BAND

Female Vocalist/Singer
July 2022 - March 2023 (9 months)
Agusan del Norte, Caraga, Philippines

I sing and perform with the band on any LGU related programs, events & private occasions.

Youfly English
English Second Language Teacher
April 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 3 months)
South Korea

I teach the English language to Korean students.

#### Concentrix

## Financial Collections Advisor I

August 2020 - February 2021 (7 months)

Makati, National Capital Region, Philippines

I was tasked to assist customers with their financial/banking concerns particularly in Collections through outbound voice support.

Amazon Operation Services Philippines, Inc. Customer Service Associate September 2019 - February 2020 (6 months)

National Capital Region, Philippines

I was tasked to provide inbound customer service through voice and chat support for online shopping customers.

### ibex

**Email Support Representative** 

May 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 4 months)

National Capital Region, Philippines

I was tasked to provide inbound customer service through email support for a ridesharing app drivers and passengers.

### 51Talk

English Second Language Teacher July 2017 - January 2018 (7 months) Philippines

I teach the English language at home to Chinese Students.

### Motive

Sales Development Representative

November 2017 - December 2017 (2 months)

San Francisco, California, United States

I was tasked to generate and qualify leads through cold calling and email campaigns. Sourcing new sales prospects.

Convergys Cebu
Technical Support Representative
April 2016 - July 2016 (4 months)
Cebu, Central Visayas, Philippines

ocou, ochtrar visayas, i imppines

I was tasked to provide inbound technical support for gaming/entertainment customers.

## Convergys Cebu

### Customer Care Representative April 2015 - October 2015 (7 months)

Cebu, Central Visayas, Philippines

I was tasked to provide inbound customer service such as billing inquiries, sales and basic technical support for telecommunication customers.

Sitel Philippines
Customer Service Representative
April 2013 - July 2014 (1 year 4 months)
Philippines

I was tasked to provide inbound customer service and support to different lines of businesses such as telecommunication, online sales and banking/financial accounts.

Greenwich - Jollibee Foods Corporation Fast Food Cashier December 2009 - February 2010 (3 months) Tacloban, Eastern Visayas, Philippines

Customer Service, taking orders from customers & handling all the cash, cheque, & debit/credit card transactions.

### PISCO COPY AND PRINTSHOP

Office Assistant

June 2009 - October 2009 (5 months)

Parañaque, National Capital Region, Philippines

Customer Service, Filing documents, Telephone operator, Custodian care, Fax, E-mail, Layout

## Education

**ACLC College** 

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (June 2007 - April 2009)